Okay, these are unbelievably expensive and I know he's going to grow out of them in like
20 minutes, but I couldn't resist
Oh, look at these
看看這些！
Oh, hey Ben, just do it
嗨，班, 做了就對！ （耐吉廣告詞）
Oh my God
喔，天啊！
Oh, okay
Was that too much pressure for him?
是不是對他壓力太大？
Oh, wow, is he hungry already?
他已經餓了嗎？
I guess so
我想是的
You know, it's something funny about sneakers
你知道，那個…球鞋真的很有趣
I'll be right back
我馬上就回來！
Oh, yeah, I got to get one too
我也要一個
Hey, what are you guys doing?
你們在幹什麼？
We're just hanging out by the spoons
我們只是來看看湯匙
Ladle?
要調羹嗎？
Look, when you guys grow up, this is the most natural, beautiful thing in the world
你們成熟一點好嗎？這是世上最自然美麗的
Yeah, we know, but there's a baby sucking on it
我們知道 但現在有個嬰兒在吸它
This is my son having lunch, okay?
這是我兒子在吃午餐
It's going to happen a lot, so you better get used to it
你們最好習慣
Now, if you have any problem with it, if you're uncomfortable, just ask questions
如果你們感到不自在 發問就好
Carol's fine with it
卡蘿不介意的
Come on
Carol? Carol?
I'm wondering,could Joey ask you a question about breast-feeding?
我想問問喬伊能不能提出 關於哺乳的問題？
Sure
當然可以
Uh, does it hurt?
會不會痛？
Well, it did at first, but not anymore
剛開始會，現在不會了
Chandler?
錢德？
So, uh, how often can you do it?
你能多久喂一次？
As much as he needs.
只要他需要就可以
Oh, okay, I got one, I got one
我想到了一個問題
Uh, if he blows into one, does the other one get bigger?
如果他對一個吹氣 另一個會不會變大？
Come on
Rachel, do you have any muffins left?
Uh, yeah, I forgot which ones
Oh, you're busy, that's okay, I'll get it
Oh, thank you
Anyone else want one?
No, thanks
No, I'll take it
Oh, you're losing your apron here, let me get it
你的圍裙鬆了，我幫你繫好
Oh
There you go
好了
Thank you
謝謝
What a bitch
真是個惡婆娘！
Oh, listen, you guys
I have this friend at Bloomingdale's who's quitting tomorrow, and he wants to abuse his discount
我有朋友在布明岱爾百貨上班 明天就不幹了，他想要花掉他的折扣優待
So, anyone who wants to come with me and take advantage of it?
誰想跟我去檢便宜？
No, I can't
我不行
I have to take my grandmother to the vet
我要帶我祖母去看獸醫
Okay, um, I'll go with you
我跟你去
Great
好極了
Okay
Hi, honey
嗨，甜心
Hey, sweetums
嗨，蜜糖
And hello to the rest
哈羅，各位
Hi
Monica, what are you doing?
You can't go shopping with her
你不能跟她去逛百貨 瑞秋怎麼辦？
What about Rachel?
This is gonna be a problem, isn't it?
會有問題，對不對？
Oh, come on, you're going to Bloomingdale's with Julie?
你要跟茱莉去布明岱爾
It's like cheating on Rachel in her house of worship
就像是到瑞秋家中偷漢子！
But I just like Monica
She will kill you
她會宰了你
She will kill you like a dog in the street
她會宰了你 就像宰街上的流浪狗！
So, uh, Jules tells me you guys are going shopping tomorrow?
茱莉說你們明天要去逛街
Oh, yeah, um, it's actually not that big a deal
其實沒有什麼…
Well, it's a big deal to me
對我很重要，非常重要
This is great, Monica
I really appreciate this
我非常感激你這麼做
You're welcome
別客氣
Woof, woof!
Pssst!
Bijan for men?
碧而泉男性香水？
Hey, Annabelle
嗨，安娜貝
Hey, Joey
嗨，喬伊
Did you hear about the new guy?
聽說過新來的人嗎？
Who?
Nobody knows his name
沒人知道他的名字
Me and the girls call him "The Hombre Man. "
我們女生都叫他「原野奇俠」
Hombre?
原野奇俠？
What's he doing in my section?
他到我這一區幹什麼？
I guess he doesn't know
我想他不知道
Well, he's gonna
他必須知道
I'll see you a little later, okay?
待會見
Hey, how you doing?
你好嗎？
Morning
早
Listen, uh, I know you're new
聽著，我知道你是新來的…
but, uh, it's kind of understood
但眾所皆知這附近的一切…
that everything from young mans to the escalator
從年輕人部門到電梯…
is, uh, my territory
都是我的地盤
Your territory, huh?
你的地盤？
Yeah
-Bijan for men?
碧而泉男性香水？
No, thanks
不，謝了
Hombre?
原野奇俠？
Yeah, all right
好啊
You were saying?
你剛才說什麼？
Phoebe, all right, listen
菲比，聽著
You were with me, and we were shopping all day
你跟我一起 逛了整天街買東西
What?
We were shopping, and we had lunch
我們買東西，吃午餐
Oh, all right, what did I have?
我吃了什麼？
You had a salad
你吃了沙拉
No wonder I don't feel full
難怪我覺得餓
Hi, guys, what's up?
嗨，怎麼樣？
I went shopping with Monica all day
我整天都跟摩妮卡買東西
and I had a salad
吃了一客沙拉
Good, Phoebs
很好，菲比
What'd you buy?
你們買了什麼？
Um, we went shopping for, um
我們去買了…
for....
嗯…
For fur.
買了皮毛
You went shopping for fur?
你去買皮毛？
Yeah
And then I realized that I'm against that
然後我發現我反對買皮毛
and, um, so then we bought some, um
於是我們買了一些…
um, boobs
波霸
Ha-ha-ha
You bought boobs?
你買了波霸？
Bras!
胸罩！
We bought bras!
我們買了胸罩！
We bought bras.
我們買了胸罩
Bijan for men?
碧而泉男性香水？
Bijan for....
碧而泉…
Hey, Annabel, uh, listen
嗨，安娜貝
I was wondering if maybe after work
我覺得下班後
you and I could go out and grab a cup of coffee
我們可以喝個咖啡嗎？
Actually, I sort of have plans
Oh
You ready, Annabel?
準備好了嗎，安娜貝？
You bet
好了
Maybe some other time
以後再約吧
Yeah
Hey, it's not the first time I lost a girl to a cowboy spraying cologne
我又不是沒被噴香水的牛仔 搶走女孩子過
Bijan for men?
碧而泉男性香水？
Bijan for men!
碧而泉男性香水！
Okay, and this is Funny Clown
這是滑稽小丑
It's only for after his naps, not before his naps, or he won't sleep.
只有睡過午覺才可以給他玩 否則他會睡不著
Carol, we've been through this before, okay?
我帶過他
We have a good time
我們玩得很高興
We laugh, we play
我們又笑又玩
It's like we're father and son
就像父親跟兒子一樣
Honey, relax
甜心，放輕鬆
Ross is great with kids
羅斯很會帶他
I'm with him
Don't look so surprised
別這麼驚訝
I'm a lovely person
我是個很好的人
Oh, this is so cute
好可愛！
Oh, I got that for him
我為他買的！
My Mommies Love Me.
「我的媽媽們愛我」
That's clever
真聰明
Hello?
Oh, hi, Jew
Hi, Jew
Uh-huh
Okay, um, sure
好的，可以
That'd be great
很好
See you then
待會見
Bye
Did you just say, hi, Jew?
你剛才是不是說： 嗨，猶太人？
Yes
Um, yes, I did
對，我是這麼說
That was my friend Eddie Moskowitz.
那是我的猶太朋友 艾迪莫斯考維茲
He's going through this whole religious thing
Yeah, he likes it
他很喜歡這稱呼
Reaffirms his faith
能加強他的信仰
Ben, dinner!
班，吃晚餐了！
Thanks, Aunt Pheebs
謝謝，菲比姑媽
Hey, you didn't microwave that, did you?
你沒有用微波爐吧？
You can't do that to breast milk.
不應該這樣處理母乳
Duh, I think I know how to heat breast milk
我想我知道如何加熱母乳
Okay
What did you just do?
你在幹什麼？
I just licked my arm, what?
我舔了我的手臂，怎麼樣？
It's breast milk
那是母乳！
So?
又怎麼樣？
Phoebe,that is juice squeezed from a person.
菲比 那是從另一個人身上擠出的汁
What is the big deal?
有什麼了不起？
No, no, Jew
That was my drink
Duh, what did you just do?
你又在幹什麼？
Can people stop drinking the breast milk?
大家能不能不要喝母乳？
You won't even taste it?
你連嘗都不嘗？
No
Not even if you just pretend that it's milk?
不能假裝那是牛奶嗎？
Not even if Carol's breast had a picture of a missing child on it?
就算卡蘿的乳房 帖了牛奶尋人廣告都不行！
Hey
Where is everybody?
大家到哪裡去了？
They took Ben to the park
帶班去公園了
Where have you been?
你去哪裡了？
Just out
出去
Had some lunch
吃了午餐
Just me
只有我一個人
A little quality time with me
與自己共度美好時光
Hey, thanks for your jacket
謝謝你的外套
Oh, no problem
別客氣
You can borrow it, by the way
你也可以向我借
Oh, here are your keys, honey
這是你的鑰匙
Thank you
Mom?
Mm-hmm?
If you were at lunch alone, how come it cost you $53?
如果你一個人吃午餐 怎麼會要五十三塊？
You know what probably happened?
你知道大概發生什麼事嗎？
Someone must have stolen my credit card.
一定有人偷了我的信用卡
And sort of just put the receipt back in your pocket?
然後把收據放回你口袋？
Huh
That is an excellent, excellent question.
這是個非常好的問題
That is excellent
真的非常好
Monica, what's with you?
你怎麼了？
Who did you have lunch with?
跟誰吃午餐？
Judy
Who?
Julie
What?
Jody
You were with Julie?
你跟茱莉在一起？
Oh, look
When it started, I was just trying to be nice to her because she was my brother's girlfriend
剛開始我只是想對她友善點…因為她是我哥哥的女友
And then one thing led to another, and before I knew it, we were
然後事情接著發生…我還不清楚，我們就…
Shopping
去瞎拼了
Oh, my God
我的天！
Honey, wait
We only did it once
慢著，我們只做了一次
It meant nothing to me!
對我沒有任何意義！
Yeah, right
Really?
Sure
Rachel, I was thinking of you the whole time
我一直想的是你！
Look, I'm sorry, all right?
對不起，好嗎？
I never meant for you to find out
我不希望你知道的
Oh, please
拜託！
Please, you wanted to get caught
你希望被逮到！
That is not true
才不是！
Oh, so you just sort of happened to leave it in here?
所以你不小心留收據在這裡？
Did it ever occur to you that I might just be that stupid?
你有沒有想到 我會這麼笨？
Okay, Monica, I just have to know one thing
好，我必須知道一件事
Did you go with her to Bloomingdale's?
你是不是跟她去布明岱爾？
Thank you
Okay
Okay, I just really, um, I just really need to not be with you right now
我現在不能跟你在一起了
Hi, who's this?
嗨，哪一位？
Hi, Joanne
嗨，瓊安
Joanne, is Rachel working?
瑞秋在嗎？
It's Monica
我是摩妮卡
Yes, I know I did a horrible thing
我知道我做了很糟糕的事
Joanne, it's not as simple as all that, okay?
瓊安，事情沒這麼簡單
No, I don't care what Steve thinks
我才不在乎史提夫怎麼想 嗨，史提夫
Hi, Steve
Hey
How did we do?
情況如何？
Oh, I tasted Ben's milk and Ross freaked out
我嘗了班的奶水 羅斯發癲了
I did not freak out
我沒有發癲
Why'd you freak out?
你為什麼發癲？
Because it's breast milk
因為那是母乳
It's gross
很噁心！
My breast milk is gross?
我的奶水很噁心？
This should be fun
這會很好玩
No, no, Carol, there's nothing wrong with it
這沒什麼不對
I just, I just don't think breast milk is for adults
我只是不認為 母乳是給大人喝的
Of course, the packaging does appeal to grown-ups and kids.
當然母乳的容器 很吸引大人與小孩
Ross, Don't be silly.
別傻了
I've tried it
我試過
It's no big deal
沒什麼
Come on, just taste it
嘗一嘗
That would be no
不行
Come on, try it
來嘛 嘗一嘗
No
It doesn't taste bad
又不難吃
Yeah,it tastes kind of sweet. Sort of like....
有一點甜，很像…
Cantaloupe juice.
哈密瓜汁
Exactly
沒錯
You've tasted it?
你嘗過了
You've, you've, you've tasted it?
Uh-huh
Oh, you've tasted it
喔，你嘗過了
You can keep saying it, but it won't stop being true
你可以一直說下去 也不會變成假話
Get me the bottle
把奶瓶給我
Get me the towel
把毛巾給我
Howdy
吃飽沒？
Get me a box of juice
給我一罐果汁
Well,they switched me over to Hombre.
他們把我調到原野奇俠了
Well, maybe it's because of the way you're dressed
也許是因為你的穿著
Or maybe it's because this guy's doing so good, they want to put more people on it
或因為那傢伙表現太好了 他們要增加人手
You should see this guy, Chandler
He goes through, like, two bottles a day now
那傢伙一天用掉兩瓶
What do you care?
你在乎什麼？
You're an actor
你是個演員
This is your day job
這只是你的副業
This isn't supposed to mean anything to you
I know, but I was the best
我知道，但我本來是最棒的
You know, I liked being the best
我喜歡當最棒的
I don't know, maybe I should just get out of the game
我不知道。也許我應該退出江湖
They need guys up in housewares to serve cheese
廚具部門需要有人切乳酪
All right, say you do that
假如你這麼做了
And then where are you going to run?
那時候你要逃到哪裡？
Yeah, I guess you're right
也許你說得對
You're damn right I'm right
I say you show this guy what you're made of. I say you stand your ground
我說你應該發揮大丈夫氣概
Show him that you're the baddest Hombre west of the lingerie!
讓他知道你是內衣部西邊 最厲害的原野奇俠！
I'm going to do it
我要這麼做！
All right
好極了
Now go see Miss Kitty, and she'll fix you up with a nice hooker
現在去找貓咪小姐 她會介紹個好妓女給你
I don't know what else to say
我不知道該說什麼
Oh, well, that works out good, because I'm not listening
很好，因為我不會聽
I feel terrible
我覺得很糟糕
I really do
真的
Oh, I'm sorry
對不起
Did my back hurt your knife?
我的背傷害了你的刀嗎？
Rachel, say that I'm friends with her. We spend some time together, Is that so terrible?
Yes
It's that terrible?
Yes, Monica, you don't get it
It's bad enough that she stole the guy who might actually be the person that I am supposed to be with
她偷走我的男人已經夠糟了…我可能會跟他長相廝守
But now she's actually stealing you
但現在…她竟然…現在她竟然連你也搶走了！
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼？
Nobody could steal me from you
沒人能把我從你那裡搶走
I mean, just because I'm friends with her doesn't make me any less friends with you
我與她交朋友 不會影響我與你的感情
I mean, you're my
你是我的…
I'm weird
Oh, I love you
I love you, too
You guys, I know that this really doesn't have anything to do with me, but I love you guys, too
喂，我知道這與我完全無關，但我也愛你們！
I really needed that
我很需要這樣
Look, I know that you're in a place right now where you really need to hate Julie's guts, but she didn't do anything wrong
我知道現在…你很想恨死茱莉，但她沒有做什麼錯事
I mean, she's just a girl who met a guy and now they go out
她只是認識了一個男生 現在他們在交往
And I really think that if you gave her a chance, you'd like her
我想如果你給她一個機會 你會喜歡她的
Will you just give that a chance?
你願意給她一個機會嗎？
I'd do anything for you, you know that!
我願意為你做任何事 你知道的
I'd do anything for you!
我什麼都願意為你做！
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
等一下！
Morning
早
I said, morning
我說：早！
I heard you
我聽見了
All right, everybody, I'm opening the doors
好，各位 我要開門了
You boys ready?
你們準備好了嗎？
Ready
好了
Yeah, I'm ready
我也好了
You idiot, you stupid cowboy!
你這個白癡！ 笨牛仔！
You blinded me!
你弄瞎我了！
I'm suing!
我要告你們！
Oh, my God!
天啊！
Todd!
陶德！
What the hell did you do?
你在搞什麼鬼！
I'm sorry
對不起
I'm such a doofus
我真是笨手笨腳！
I'm so sorry
對不起
非常對不起
My God, what happened?
老天，發生什麼事？
These new kids, they never last
這些菜鳥，都撐不了很久
Sooner or later, they all stop lasting
遲早他們就會……捅出紕漏
What do you say I buy you that cup of coffee now?
我們去喝杯咖啡怎麼樣？
Sure
好啊
So
I just thought the two of us should hang out for a bit
我想我們應該親近親近
I mean, you know, we've never really talked
你知道的 我們從來沒有真正談過話
I guess you'd know, that being one of the two of us, right?
我想你說得對 因為你是我們兩個之一
I know
我知道
I probably shouldn't even tell you this, but I'm pretty much totally intimidated by you
我也許不該告訴你…但我實在很怕你
Really?
真的？
Me?
怕我？
Oh, my God, are you kidding?
你在開玩笑嗎？
Ross is so crazy about you, and I really wanted you to like me, and I
羅斯還是對你很著迷…我真的希望你喜歡我
It's probably me just being totally paranoid, but I kind of got the feeling that maybe you don't
也許我只是胡思亂想…但我好像覺得你不喜歡我
Well
You're not totally paranoid
你不是完全胡思亂想
Oy
Um
Okay, um
God
Um
When you and, uh, Ross first started going out, it was really hard for me
當你與羅斯剛開始交往時…我真的很難過…
Um
For many reasons, of which I'm not gonna bore you with now
有太多理由，我不要煩你
But, um
I just, I see how happy he is, you know, and how good you guys are together
但我看到他非常快樂 而且你們在一起是多麼相配
And, um
Monica's always saying how nice you are, and God, I hate it when she's right
摩妮卡一直說你有多好…我真討厭她說得對！
Thanks
謝謝
Hey, listen, would you like to go to a movie sometime or something?
你想不想一起去看電影 或出去玩？
Yeah, that'd be great
這樣很好
Yeah?
I'd love it
我很樂意
I'd love it, too
我也是
Okay
Oh, shoot, I gotta go
我必須要走了
Okay
So, I'll talk to you later, okay?
待會見
All right, Julie
好，茱莉
Bye
What a manipulative bitch
真是個玩弄人的賤人！
It's not bad.
還不錯